kvcwebhost.com 2018-09-10

# KVCHOSTING Privacy Policy

## KVCHOSTING.NET Privacy Policy  
& GDPR COMPLIANCE

KVCHosting.net, LLC is committed to protecting client data collected. KVCHosting respects client's privacy and use of KVCHosting services indicates agreement to KVCHosting privacy policy guidelines as defined:

KVCHosting will collect and record minimum required client information in order to provide competitive services. KVCHosting privacy policy states the kinds of processes that may occur in different circumstances when client data will be collected. Usage of KVCHosting.net grants the right to collect user information. 

KVCHosting may record any or all information given by client according to transaction type client enters, such as date of birth, name, address, phone numbers, fax numbers, email addresses, website use, and other personal information needed to process request. 

KVCHosting will strictly use required information and data on client to process request or task made. KVCHosting will enforce reasonable measures needed to prevent unauthorized access to such information. In certain cases, KVCHosting may require additional forms of identity from client to safeguard such information. 

Client internet browsers have in-built mechanisms to store small files or cookies that have information to help websites recognise client account. KVCHosting may use such facility to increase user experience. However, user may choose to prevent user computer from accepting cookies, which may impair some of the website's functions. 

KVCHosting will not disclose any personal information received from client to third parties. KVCHosting may use such information to notify or inform client about developments and other KVCHosting services or offers. However, client or user will be given the option to remove self from such a mailing list or notification processes. KVCHosting will not disclose information collected on website to third parties without consent and acknowledgement from client/user. KVCHosting may provide general survey or data information to third parties but will withhold those that may identify individuals. 

**U.S.-EU & U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks**  
KVC Hosting complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. KVC Hosting has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view KVC Hosting's certification, please visit [//www.export.gov/safeharbor/](https://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

**DISCLOSURE TO LAW ENFORCEMENT**  
KVCHosting reserves the right to disclose subscriber information to law enforcement agencies without consent or notifying subscriber if lawful request is made from such agencies. KVCHosting will cooperate fully with such law enforcement agencies. 

**POLICY CHANGES**  
KVCHosting may change its Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Reasonable steps will be made to inform clients/users. However, clients are encouraged to check for updates every time they enter the website to ensure it meets their approval. Changes will be made directly to Privacy policy and such future changes will supersede the prior version. 

**CONTACT US**   
Clients and users are encouraged to contact KVCHosting directly if any questions should arise or they need clarification about information collected. Factual errors in such information or removal of details from list under KVCHosting may also be made this way.

**TYPE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
We collect certain personal information about visitors and users of our Sites.  
The most common types of information we collect include things like: user-names, member names, email addresses, IP addresses, other contact details, survey responses, blogs, photos, payment information such as payment agent details, transactional details, tax information, support queries, forum comments, content you direct us to make available on our Sites (such as item descriptions) and web analytics data. We will also collect personal information from job applications (such as, your CV, the application form itself, cover letter and interview notes).

**HOW WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION  
** We collect personal information directly when you provide it to us, automatically as you navigate through the Sites, or through other people when you use services associated with the Sites. We collect your personal information when you provide it to us when you complete membership registration and buy or provide items or services on our Sites, subscribe to a newsletter, email list, submit feedback, enter a contest, fill out a survey, or send us a communication. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOUR FROM OTHERS  
**Although we generally collect personal information directly from you, on occasion, we also collect certain categories of personal information about you from other sources. In particular:

  1. financial and/or transaction details from payment providers located in the US, UK, and Australia in order to process a transaction;  
 
  2. third party service providers (like Google, Facebook) who are located in the US or UK, which may provide information about you when you link, connect, or login to your account with the third party provider and they send us information such as your registration and profile from that service, this only occurs if you are using Envato Studio. The information varies and is controlled by that service provider or as authorized by you via your privacy settings at that service provider; and  
 
  3. other third party sources/ and or partners from Australia, US or UK, whereby we receive additional information about you (to the extent permitted by applicable law), such as demographic data or fraud detection information, and combine it with information we have about you. For example, fraud warnings from service providers like identity verification service. We also receive information about you and your activities on and off the Envato platform through partnerships, or about your experiences and interactions from our partner ad networks. We also receive information about you as a rights holder from our third party authors. For example, information in the form of a model release when your image is used in an item made available on our Sites.

**HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION  
**

  * To fulfil a contract, or take steps linked to a contract: in particular, in facilitating and processing transactions that take place on the Sites, like where you purchase your hosting from KVCHOSTING.NET 
  * operating the Sites;
  * providing you with services described on the Sites;
  * verifying your identity when you sign in to any of our Sites;
  * responding to support tickets, and helping facilitate the resolution of any disputes;
  * updating you with operational news and information about our Sites and services e.g. to notify you about changes to our Sites, website disruptions or security updates;
  * carrying out technical analysis to determine how to improve the Sites and services we provide;
  * monitoring activity on the Sites, e.g. to identify potential fraudulent activity and to ensure compliance with the user terms that apply to the Sites;
  * managing our relationship with you, e.g. by responding to your comments or queries submitted to us on the Sites or asking for your feedback or whether you want to participate in a survey;
  * managing our legal and operational affairs (including, managing risks relating to content and fraud matters);
  * training Envato staff about how to best serve our user community;
  * improving our products and services.
  * providing general administrative and performance functions and activities.

**WHERE YOU GIVE US CONSENT**

  * providing you with marketing information about products and services which we feel may interest you; and
  * customising our services and websites, like advertising that appear on the Site - where this involves the use of cookies or similar technologies - in order to provide a more personalised experience.
  * For purposes which are required by law.
  * For the purpose of responding to requests by government, a court of law, or law enforcement authorities conducting an investigation.

**WHEN WE DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We will disclose personal information to the following recipients: 

  1. KVCHOSTING.NET which are located in the US;
authors of any items or services made available to you, so they can facilitate support and license validation, who maybe located in any of the countries our products are available in; subcontractors and service providers who assist us in connection with the ways we use personal information (as set out above), in particular: website hosting providers which are located in Australia, US and UK; technical and customer support services which are located in Australia, Canada, Philippines, Poland, Mexico, Romania, UK and the US; recruitment agencies which are located in Australia, US and Mexico; marketing and analytics services which are located in the US; security and fraud prevention services which are located in the US; subscription management services which are located in the US; payment processing services which are located in the US, UK and Australia; identification verification services located in the UK; and operational tooling services which are located in the US. Noting that our subcontractors and services providers may also transfer and access such information from other countries in which they have operations. 
  2. our professional advisers (lawyers, accountants, financial advisers etc.) which are located in USA;
  3. regulators and government authorities in connection with our compliance procedures and obligations;
  4. a purchaser or prospective purchaser of all or part of our assets or our business, and their professional advisers, in connection with the purchase;
  5. a third party to respond to requests relating to a criminal investigation or alleged or suspected illegal activity;
  6. a third party, in order to enforce or defend our rights, or to address financial or reputational risks;
  7. a rights holder in relation to an allegation of intellectual property infringement or any other infringement; and
  8. other recipients where we are authorised or required by law to do so.

**WHERE WE TRANSFER AND/OR STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
We are based in USA so your data will be processed in USA. Some of the recipients we have described in above, and to whom we disclose your personal information, are based outside USA in places like Canada, Ireland, Philippines, Poland, Romania, UK, and the AUSTRALIA. We do this on the basis of your consent to this policy. In order to protect your information, we take care where possible to work with subcontractors and service providers who we believe maintain an acceptable standard of data security compliance. 

**HOW WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE**  
We store personal information on secure servers that are managed by us and our service providers, and occasionally hard copy files that are kept in a secure location in USA. Personal information that we store or transmit is protected by security and access controls, including username and password authentication, two-factor authentication, and data encryption where appropriate. 

**HOW YOU CAN ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**   
You can access some of the personal information that we collect about you by logging in to your client area. You also have the right to make a request to access other personal information we hold about you and to request corrections of any errors in that data. You can also close the account you have with us for any of our Sites at any time. To make an access or correction request, contact our privacy helpdesk using the contact details at the end of this policy.

**MARKETING CHOICES REGARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

  1. Where we have your consent to do so (e.g. if you have subscribed to one of our e-mail lists or have indicated that you are interested in receiving offers or information from us), we send you marketing communications by email about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. You can 'opt-out' of such communications if you would prefer not to receive them in the future by using the "unsubscribe" facility provided in the communication itself.
  2. You also have choices about cookies, as described below. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject cookies some parts of our Sites may not work properly in your case.

**Cookies (not the type you eat!) and web analytics**  
For more information about how we use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies see our cookie policy here and for more general information on cookies, see [http://www.allaboutcookies.org.](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

When you visit our Sites, there's certain information that's recorded which is generally anonymous information and does not reveal your identity. If you're logged into your account some of this information could be associated with your account. We're talking about the following kinds of details: 

  1. your IP address or proxy server IP address';
  2. the domain name you requested;
  3. the name of your internet service provider is sometimes captured depending on the configuration of your ISP connection;
  4. the date and time of your visit to the website;
  5. the length of your session;
  6. the pages which you have accessed;
  7. the number of times you access our site within any month;
  8. the file URL you look at and information relating to it;
  9. the website which referred you to our Sites; and
  10. the operating system which your computer uses.

Occasionally, we will use third party advertising companies to serve ads based on prior visits to our Sites. For example, if you visit our Sites, you may later see an add for our products and services when you visit a different Site.

**INFORMATION ABOUT CHILDREN**  
Our Sites are not suitable for children under the age of 16 years, so if you are under 16 we ask that you do not use our Sites or give us your personal information (if you are a young tech wiz, please direct your nearest responsible adult to use the Sites for you!). If you are from 16 to 18 years, you can browse the Sites but you'll need the supervision of a parent or guardian to become a registered user. It's the responsibility of parents or guardians to monitor their children's use of our Sites. 

**INFORMATION YOU MAKE PUBLIC OR GIVE TO OTHERS**  
If you make your personal information available to other people, we can't control or accept responsibility for the way they will use or manage that data. There are lots of ways that you can find yourself providing information to other people, like when you post a public message on a forum thread, share information via social media, or make contact with another user (such as a third party Author) whether via our Sites or directly via email. Before making your information publicly available or giving your information to anyone else, think carefully. If giving information to another user via our Sites, ask them how they will handle your information. If you're sharing information via another website, check the privacy policy for that site to understand its information management practices as this privacy policy will not apply. 

**HOW LONG WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
We retain your personal information for as long as is necessary to provide the services to you and others, and to comply with our legal obligations. If you no longer want us to use your personal information or to provide you with the KVCHOSTING  services, you can request that we erase your personal information and close your KVCHOSTING account. Please note that if you request the erasure of your personal information we will retain information from deleted accounts as necessary for our legitimate business interests, to comply with the law, prevent fraud, collect fees, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with investigations, enforce the terms of service and take other actions permitted by law. The information we retain will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**WHEN WE NEED TO UPDATE THIS POLICY**  
We will need to change this policy from time to time in order to make sure it stays up to date with the latest legal requirements and any changes to our privacy management practices.

When we do change the policy, we'll make sure to notify you about such changes, where required. A copy of the latest version of this policy will always be available on this page.

**HOW YOU CAN CONTACT US**  
if you have any questions about our privacy practices or the way in which we have been managing your personal information, please contact our privacy champion in writing at 3030 NW Expressway Suite #200, Oklahoma City, OK 73112 - USA or privacy@kvchosting.net. We're really glad you made it to the end of the privacy policy, because knowing this stuff is the best way to understand how your personal information is used and how to best manage it!

**IF YOU'RE A USER OR VISITOR IN THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA THESE RIGHT ALSO APPLY TO YOU:**   
For the purposes of applicable EU data protection law (including the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (the " **GDPR** "), we are a 'data controller' of your personal information.

**HOW CAN YOU ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

  * You are also entitled to ask us to port your personal information (i.e. to transfer in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, to you), to erase it, or restrict its processing. You also have rights to object to some processing that is based on our legitimate interests, such as profiling that we perform for the purposes of direct marketing, and, where we have asked for your consent to process your data, to withdraw this consent as more fully described below.
  * These rights are limited in some situations - for example, we can demonstrate that we have a legal requirement to process your personal information. In some instances, this means that we may retain some data even if you withdraw your consent.
  * Where we require your personal information to comply with legal or contractual obligations, then provision of such data is mandatory: if such data is not provided, then we will not be able to manage our contractual relationship with you, or to meet obligations placed on us. In all other cases, provision of requested personal information is optional.
  * If you have unresolved concerns you also have the right to complain to data protection authorities. The relevant data protection authority will be the data protection authority of the country: (i) of your habitual residence; (ii) of your place of work; or (iii) in which you consider the alleged infringement has occurred.

**Both personal information and personal data have the same meaning in the context of this Privacy Policy. KVCHOSTING Privacy Policy, effective date 25 May 2018**

### **2018 HOSTING REVIEWS**

Our reputation of excellence is unmatched - we pride ourselves on being experts that our clients can depend on for whatever they need

## Our Awards

**2018 HOSTING ACHIEVEMENTS**

We have received many awards in our 8+ years of providing web hosting service

## Testimonial

.......................................................

__  I almost never use the word "Perfect", but here I want to say KVCHosting service is PERFECT! Even though it has been only one year I have been a customer of theirs, I can still say KVCHosting is the best and Perfect, without any doubts. Thanks for your service and fast responds. If you care about Customer Service and Stability, KVCHosting is the ideal place for you  __

.......................................................

|  Charles Griffith   
Senior Marketing Manager  
---|---  
  
.......................................................

__  I almost never use the word "Perfect", but here I want to say KVCHosting service is PERFECT! Even though it has been only one year I have been a customer of theirs, I can still say KVCHosting is the best and Perfect, without any doubts. Thanks for your service and fast responds. If you care about Customer Service and Stability, KVCHosting is the ideal place for you  __

.......................................................

---  
|  |  Charles Griffith   
Senior Marketing Manager  
---|---
